repairmymobile.in 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy - RepairMyMobile.in

http://repairmymobile.in/ has two sub-domain which are:-  
i- http://forum.repairmymobile.in/  
ii- http://directory.repairmymobile.in/

**1- What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**2- What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**3- How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**4- Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information  
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**5- DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads on Repair My Mobile. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google’s Content Network Privacy Policy.

**6- Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**7- Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**8- California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**9- Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**10- Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online [privacy policy](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/repairmymobile.in) applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**11-Reviews, Rating & Comments by users:-**

RepairMyMobile circulate information through various medium of communication which include E-Mail, SMS, Website etc. users can use any of the stated medium to post comments, post review and rating about our services and also about the Advertiser listed at Directory is subjected to additional terms & conditions mentioned below.

RepairMyMobile reserves the right not to upload or distribute to, or otherwise publish through the Site or Forums any Communication which is obscene, indecent, pornographic, profane, sexually explicit, threatening, or abusive; constitutes or contains false or misleading indications of origin or statements of fact;slanders, libels, defames, disparages, or otherwise violates the legal rights of any third party;causes injury of any kind to any person or entity;infringes or violates the intellectual property rights (including copyright, patent and trademark rights), contract rights, trade secrets, privacy or publicity rights or any other rights of any third party;violates any applicable laws, rules, or regulations;contains software viruses or any other malicious code designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;Impersonates another person or entity, or that collects or uses any information about Site visitors.

We can use your communication as per requirement from time to time. We also have the right to show or hide your identification with respect to reviews, rating & comments posted by users or advertiser.

**12- Warranty Disclaimer**

We are not responsible for any Warranty issued by the third party and if you are buying a product from us and we have offered a warranty on that product, then you have to courier the products with your cost with no physical damage.

***Software Boxes does not come with Warranty.

But when you receive the product, we will install it for the first time. In case, if it fails to run. The product will be replaced.  
***Carrier Unlock Sim like o2 & Voda doesn’t come with any warranty and no replacement if it fails to Support.

**13- Content Disclaimer on http://directory.repairmymobile.in  
**

We communicate information provided and created by advertisers, content partners, users, resellers and other third parties. Attempts are made to verify the authenticity of the shops and service center, the accuracy of such content, integrity or quality of such content and the information on our pages,  and we make no guarantees, nor can we be responsible for any such information, including its authenticity, content, quality, copyright compliance or legality, or any other intellectual property rights compliance, or any resulting loss or damage. Further, we are not liable for any kind of damages, losses or action arising directly or indirectly due to any content, including any errors or omissions in any content, access and/or use of the content on the Platforms or any of them including but not limited to content based decisions resulting in loss of data, revenue, profits, property, infection by viruses etc.

**14- Third-parties and Opt-Out**  
Third-parties may display interest-based advertising to you in applications or websites, based on your use of applications or websites over time and across non-affiliated apps.  
Such third parties may combine and use information from websites or applications on your current browser or device with information from your other browsers or devices for advertising purposes. To opt-out of such interest-based advertising and/or cross-device targeting, please use the methods provided below for opting out on each of your browsers and on each of your devices:  
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) – http://optout.networkadvertising.org/  
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) – http://www.aboutads.info/choices/  
Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC) – http://youradchoices.ca/choices  
Digital Advertising Alliance EU (EDAA) – http://www.youronlinechoices.com/  
Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising and cross-device targeting does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the third-party from which you have opted out of receiving interest-based advertising or cross-device targeting by using the methods provided above will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns on a particular web browser or device.”

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was updated on 30/10/2019.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
http://repairmymobile.in/  
info@repairmymobile.in
